这是你的账单
Here's your check.
我没收你薯条钱 因为是我吃的
I didn't charge you for the fries, 'cause I ate them.
麦克斯 小心
Max, look out!
餐厅里的小强越来越大只了
The diner water bugs are getting really big.
放轻松 这是餐厅最新的无人监视机
Relax, it's the diner's new surveillance drone.
也就把收银机里的钱清空了5次或10次
God, you empty the register five or ten times,
人跟人之间的信任突然全没了
suddenly there's no trust.
所以说 店里没肥皂 却有无人机吗
So to be clear, we're out of soap but we have a drone?
我真不爽阿憨可以坐在办公室里盯着我们
I hate that Han's just sitting in back, watching us,
然后手里玩着他的"欢乐小操控杆"
working his little joy stick.
拜托 阿憨的"小杆子"能给谁"欢乐"啊
Please, no one's getting any joy out of Han's little stick.
这也太烦人了
This is so annoying.
一直在跟着我
It's following me.
就你那扁屁股 这应该是唯一会
Well, with a butt that flat, it's the only black thing
跟踪你的黑色人事物了
that's ever going to follow you.
外面又来了一台无人机啊
Ugh, there's another drone out here?
我刚才在厨房里用苍蝇拍弄死了一台
I just killed one in the kitchen with a fly swatter.
滚
Go.
我如果这么想被人监视
I mean, if I wanted to be spied on,
我把名字换个中东名
I'd change my name to Achmed,
然后去机场附近买公寓住就好啦
and buy a condo near the airport.
买幅老船长的画挂墙上 然后墙后挖洞
Whatever happened to buying a painting of an old sea captain,
通过眼睛的洞 监看餐厅的经典招数何在
drilling out the eye holes, and hiding behind it?
这样不对 阿憨
Not cool, Han.
而且最惨的地方是 它一直动来动去
And the worst part is, it's moving around so much,
我都找不到上镜的好角度
I can't find my good angle.
这么做不对 不过不是阿憨
Not cool and not Han.
我趁他在跟我解释为什么
I stole this while he was explaining to me
一名领着最低时薪工资的77岁老头
why a 77-year-old man, on minimum wage,
不需要医疗保健时 偷了这遥控
doesn't need health care.
厄尔 这太赞了
Earl, that is awesome.
赞个毛 我很需要好吗
Not really. I need that health care.
不 我是指你偷来了遥控器
No, that you stole that.
我们需要做点什么 好让阿憨
We need to do something that will make Han
再也不想监视我们
never want to spy on us again.
奥列格 扒开你的裤子
Oleg, open your pants.
厄尔 把监视机往里面飞
Earl, fly that camera in there.
但首先 你先把内裤脱了
But first, take off your underwear.
内裤
Underwear?
不是吧 你当我5[岁]...
Come on. What am I, five?
英寸小屌男[12.7公分]吗
Inches?
奥列格 厄尔有白内障 你放心他技术吗
Oleg, aren't you at all worried about Earl's cataracts?
撞大运 那我得到免费下体除毛
Best case scenario, I get a little manscaping.
倒大霉 那我也早就想去割包皮
Worst case, I've been meaning to get circumcised.
真是瞎了眼了
My eyes!
麦克斯 我在给我们银行贷款填支票
Max, I'm writing out the check for our bank loan,
但我不太确定我们余额有多少
and I'm not quite sure what our balance is
因为在"提款"这一栏 你写了"对啊"
because here under "Withdrawals" you just wrote, "Yeah."
如果你不喜欢这个 那你更不会想看到
Well, if you don't like that, you're really not going to like
我在"存款"栏下画的图了
the picture I drew under "Deposits."
我看到了
I saw it.
麦克斯那些0不是蛋蛋 也不是奶子
Max, zeroes are not balls, they're not boobs,
也不是玩具转转眼
and they're not googly eyes.
它们就只是0而已
They're just zeroes.
你的片面之词
Says you.
我去提款机查看我们的余额吧
I'll go check our balance at the ATM.
虽然上一个用过的男的
Even though the last guy who touched it
他长的感冒疮大到
had a cold sore so big,
我得收他双人用餐的钱
I charged him for a party of two.
放心吧 你不会在那台机器上得任何东西
Don't worry. You are not going to get anything from that machine.
尤其是钱
Especially cash.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
快来人帮本宫做点鸡蛋吃
Somebody better make me some eggs
本宫开始了果汁断食整整三个小时
because I've been on a juice cleanse for three hours,
我就已经要饿晕了
and I'm dizzy.
名字里虽然说是快速
Yeah. I mean, they call it a fast,
但疗程间真是度日如年啊
but it sure does go slow.
我也曾经试过一次三周断食法
I was on a three weeks fast, once.
直到后来我才发现原来我妈不回来了
Then I realized my mother wasn't coming home.
我就给自己做了三明治
So I made a sandwich.
我与奥列格的婚礼快到了
Oleg and my wedding is coming up
而且我们也在试着吃净食
and we're trying to eat clean.
是啊 宝贝
Yeah, baby,
因为咱们蜜月时 铁定会吃得很"肮脏"
'cause you know we're eating dirty on the honeymoon.
天啊 怎么了
Oh, dear God, what?
收据那里又有用完的避孕套吗
Another used condom in the receipt slot?
-更惨 -什么
- Worse. - What?
应该在保险套里的"东西"没在里面吗
Stuff that should be in a condom but isn't?
我们的余额低于0
We're below zero.
各位 我先撤了
Oh, well, I better go, y'all.
白人女人在我附近尖叫
A white woman screaming anywhere in my vicinity
我下场从来没好过
never turns out well.
这也太惨了
This is a disaster.
我试过只剩0元
I've been at zero,
但我从没有低于0过
but I've never had less than zero.
卡洛琳 别这么说啊
Oh, don't say that, Caroline.
你忘了你能挑的男人数 也是低于0吗
I mean, you're forgetting about your dating options.
麦克斯 我们有的钱低于0啊
We have less than zero money
而且绝对付不起银行贷款
and no way of paying off our bank loan.
天啊 这终于发生了
Oh, my God. It happened.
我成了工人阶级
I'm working class.
我跟你一起当服务员四年了
Hey. I've waited tables with you for four years
就你工作哪样 绝对不够格称之为工人
and there's no way you could call what you do working.
小蛋糕
Cupcakes!
来买小蛋糕
Buy cupcakes.
给老娘买小蛋糕
Buy cupcakes!
别嚎了
Stop.
你的样子比贾斯丁·比伯在CK广告里
You look more desperate than Justin Bieber
还不要脸
in that Calvin Klein ad.
你根本不懂我们银行的事情有多严峻
You don't understand the seriousness of this bank situation.
你还不懂《魔兽世界》的规矩咧
You don't understand the rules of World Of Warcraft.
贷款的钱会越滚愈多
The loan just keeps escalating and escalating
最后他们会把我们的店查封
until they close us down.
小蛋糕 买小蛋糕
Cupcakes! Buy cupcakes!
来买小蛋糕 来买小蛋糕
Buy cupcakes! Buy cupcakes!
银子送上门了 看
Oh, Pay-dirt. Look.
来了个兄弟会大胖子
Here comes a big, fat frat house guy.
好久不见 骚货们
Hey, bitches.
还记得我吗
Remember me?
大玛丽
Big Mary.
行不改名 坐不改姓
That's my name. Don't wear it out.
烘焙学校倒了以后就没见过你了
John, we haven't seen you since pastry school.
看在往日的同窗情谊 买个小蛋糕吧
Hey, for old times' sake, want to buy a cupcake?
或来一打 还是整家店
A dozen? The shop?
我来是因为我可能有个
So I came because I may know of a way
能让麦克斯赚点外快的路子
for Max to make some extra money.
你说得出 她"做得到"
Whatever it is, she'll do it.
我毕业纪念册上就留了这句
That was my yearbook quote.
我刚被曼哈顿高线公园的
I just got hired at a new restaurant
一家新餐厅给录用了
that's opening under the High Line Park in Manhattan,
他们还想再请一名白天班烘焙师
and they are looking for another day pastry chef.
我只读过大概一年的烘焙学校
I only have a year of pastry school
而且那期间我有一年是大麻抽到晕乎
and I was stoned for, like, a year of that.
我不知道我能不能胜任那工作
I don't know if I have the skills.
妹子 你当然不能
Oh, girl, you don't.
但是那个经理 乔啊 只喜欢颜值高的人
But the manager, Joe, wants only pretty people.
你烘焙技能点不足的地方
And what you lack in pastry,
在颜值上已经大大地补上了
you more than make up for in pretty.
她会去 你得去 麦克斯
She'll do it. You'll do it, Max.
而且你有烘焙技能点高的他在身旁协助嘛
And John will be there to help back you up with his pastry skills.
姐是靠脸蛋的
And 'cause I'm pretty.
那种地方不适合我
I don't belong in a place like that.
那家店叫"嗨翻天"
It's called "The High."
这听起来就对了 把资料留给我
Sounds right. Give me the deets.
晚安啦 姑娘们
Well, good night girls.
你们的银行余额我也很遗憾
Sorry about your bank balance.
但我相信你们两个
But I trust you'll both lapse
很快能一如既往地否认事实
into denial fairly soon, as always.
你好
Hello.
她是谁啊
Who was she?
抱紧我 吻我 爱别走
Hold me closer, tiny dancer.
他不是同性恋
Oh...Han's not gay.
是他"还"不是同性恋
You forgot the "Yet."
麦克斯 你扣子要不要往上扣一两个
Max, maybe button up a button or two.
这里是甜点吧 不是脱衣酒吧
It's a dessert bar. Not a strip bar.
我需要这份工作
Hey, I need this job,
等那个乔先生看过了我这对蓬松奶酥
and once this Joe guy takes one look at these puff pastries,
他之后看到我做的"不蓬松奶酥"时
he might cut me some slack when he sees my other
就不会太计较了
"not so puff" pastries.
你心里过得去吗
And you're comfortable with that?
当然
Yup.
就跟某人靠着她那微薄的"服务"功夫
Like I guess you're comfortable applying for a waitress job
不也来应征当服务员了吗
on just the merits of your waitress skills.
我该继续往下吗
Should I keep going?
要"下"死人吗
Why?
我来了
I'm here.
申请表给我 快点 女士们
I'll take those applications. Hurry, ladies.
如果想请好看又慢[笨]的人 我会请尼克·乔纳斯
If I was looking for pretty and slow, I'd hire Nick Jonas.
麦克斯 我们还是快撤吧
Max, let's get out of here.
她让我想起一段恶梦
She reminds me of this nightmare
一段我余生都会做的一场恶梦
I'm going to have for the rest of my life.
别紧张 她只是看门狗而已
Relax, she's just his guard dog.
我们需要讨好的是乔先生
It's Joe guy we have to impress.
你请回吧
No thank you.
你也请回
你哪来的胆子来
And how dare you?
抱歉 餐厅要到明天才开幕
Oh, I'm sorry, the restaurant doesn't open until tomorrow.
不是这样的
Actually, no.
您好 我来应征服务员工作
Hi. I'm here to apply for a waitress job.
在你这年纪吗
At your age?
我27岁
I'm 27!
所以呢
And?
麦克斯 我要喘不上气了
Max, I can't breathe.
而我是来应征烘焙师的
And I'm here to apply for a pastry chef.
也是27岁 不过我打从6岁时就长这样
Also 27, but I've looked this old since I was 6.
我还曾经以为我有电影里 会返老还童的病呢
For a while, I thought I had that Benjamin Button's disease.
我先跟烘焙师谈
I'll take the pastry chef first.
你先坐过去一边等
Why don't you sit over there and wait.
我不会太久的 因为老实说
I won't be long, because frankly,
你到这岁数 也等不起了
you don't have the time.
谢谢你 我就在这里
Thank you. I'll be over there.
申请社保[特别照顾老人残疾人等]
Applying for Social Security.
所以你是去哪上的烘焙学校
So where did you go to pastry school,
还有 你为什么现在没工作呢
and why aren't you working now?
曼哈顿烘焙学院 我有工作
Manhattan School Of Pastry, and I am working.
我在布鲁克林有一家自己的小蛋糕店
I have my own cupcake shop in Brooklyn.
快结束了
Oh, it's almost over.
面试吗 太好了
This interview? Great.
不 不是面试 是布鲁克林
No. Not the interview. Brooklyn.
布鲁克林就快结束了
Brooklyn's almost over.
还有 小蛋糕也要过时了
Also, cupcakes.
真酷 我会告诉他们的
Cool. I will tell them.
真希望我能早点知道这事
Wish I knew that before they all got
这样他们就不用都跑去穿脐环装酷了
their belly buttons pierced trying to stay cool.
很好 有幽默感
Oh, great. A sense of humor.
顾客们会喜欢的
Customers love that.
我不喜欢 但他们喜欢
I don't, but they do.
所以负责请人的这个乔先生在那里呢
So, um, where's this Joe guy who's doing the hiring?
没有"乔先生" 我就是乔啊
There is no "Joe guy." I'm Joe.
是乔 啊
Spelled, J-O-E-D-T-H.
啊是无声气音
The D-T-H is silent.
我也无话可说 因为我想要这份工作
As am I, because I want this job.
那看来我可以把这些收起来了
Well, I guess I can put these away then.
你本来打算靠这个吗
That was your plan?
亮出你的胸器好勾来一份工作
To expose your breasts and seduce your way into this job?
你说得好像这是件坏事
You say that like it's a bad thing.
好啦 再见
Okay. Well, bye.
坐下 坐
Sit, sit.
如果你真的懂烘焙
If you really can bake,
那这个职位可能非常适合你
this position might be perfect for you.
而且 你有一种很犀利
Also, you have that edgy,
"我才懒得鸟你"的态度
"I don't give a crap" attitude.
顾客们就爱这套
Customers love that.
我不喜欢 但他们喜欢
I don't, but they do.
其实 乔 无声啊 我会烘焙
Actually, Joe, silent D-T-H, I can bake.
技术有多好
But how well?
我女朋友跟我非常超爱法式甜馅饼
My girlfriend and I are obsessed with French pastry.
女朋友是指那种"女朋友"
Oh. Girlfriend as in "Girlfriend,"
还是两位处于某个年龄阶层
or as in two ladies of a certain age
在电影院分享爆米花吃的女性朋友
at a Cineplex splitting one thing of popcorn?
你刚才说的一切都冒犯了我
Everything you just said offended me.
那是我这人的招牌
Yeah, that's my brand.
而鉴于刚才你并没有对
And the fact that you didn't cry
分享爆米花的事表示不满
about splitting a popcorn makes me think
我猜你的是第一种"女朋友"
it's the first kind of girlfriend.
你的马卡龙怎么样
How are your macaroons?
我的马卡龙吗
My macaroons?
非常软滑
Great.
一抹法式天堂般的感觉
A little bit of French heaven.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
麦克斯
Max.
麦 克 斯
M-a-x.
没有无声音 全得"叫出来"
Nothing is silent. Ever.
我也发现了
So I gather.
好了 你去填申请表吧 麦克斯
Okay. Why don't you go fill out an application, Max.
你可以把咪咪也收起来了
And you can put those away again.
我对巨乳妹没兴趣
I'm really not into big-breasted women.
妹子 你肯定手到擒来
Girl, you got this.
第一天上班 你紧张不 大妹子
First day. Are you nervous, girl?
拜托 紧张是用来形容在你三个哥哥出柜后
Please. Nervous is telling your elderly Mormon parents
你要向年迈的摩门教父母坦诚
that you're gay after your three older siblings
你也基时的心情
already came out.
这里大部分甜点我都不知道是什么
I have no idea what most of these desserts are.
感觉比《迷失》的大结局还让人迷失
I haven't felt this lost since the finale of Lost.
麦克斯 你能看见衣服上有高级百货店的价签吗
Max, can you see any of the Barney's price tags on these?
那有个凸出来的价签
Uh, I think there's one bunching up
在你裤子里的后面
inside the back of your pants.
不 那是内裤 回头也得退
No, that's the underwear I'm also returning.
她来了
Here she comes.
姑娘们 这位是娜奥米
Hi, ladies. This is Naomi,
甜点吧的领座员
the dessert bar hostess.
去啊 娜奥米 快去
Go, Naomi, go.
漂亮 但跟现在最炙手可热的傻逼名人一样蠢
Gorgeous, but as dumb as whoever is the hot new idiot right now.
出来让我看看你
Let me take a look at you.
可以走了
Good-bye.
这么快
Already?
珍珠项链 必须摘下
Those pearls. They have to go.
真的吗 可是...
Really? It's just, well,
我对这串项链有很深的感情
I'm kind of emotionally attached to them.
亲爱的 我很爱我那只半瞎的法国斗牛犬
Well, honey, I love my half-blind French bulldog,
但我不会把她戴在脖子上啊
but I don't wear her around my neck.
麦克斯 让我看看你
Max, let me take a look.
我喜欢
Love it.
超赞 干得好
Fabulous. Well done.
乔啊 今天是大日子 我好兴奋哦
Hi, Joe. Big day. I'm so excited.
那你进后厨兴奋吧 姑娘
Why don't you be excited in the back, doll?
我要麦克斯在前台
I want Max up front now.
在一生中 人们总是告诉我不要出来[柜]
All my life, people have been telling me not to come out.
这里的人们也一样
Why should here be any different?
姑娘们 我刚刚得到消息
Ladies, I just got word
《纽约时报》的美食评论家
that the New York Times food critic
今天下午可能会来暗访
may make a surprise visit this afternoon.
一切都要做到完美
Everything has to be perfect--
服务 甜点
the service, the desserts,
我不稳定的药量平衡
the precarious balance of my meds.
不容有半点差错
Nothing can go wrong.
娜奥米
Naomi.
"接"客啊
Fetch.
"欢迎来到嗨翻天"
"Welcome to The High."
"嗨 欢迎来到嗨翻天"
"Hi. Welcome to The High."
"欢迎来到嗨翻天"
"Welcome to The High."
别再说"嗨"这个词了 我没嗑药不嗨
Stop saying high. It reminds me I'm not.
等等 麦克斯 你不嗨吗
Wait, Max, you're not high?
一丁点都没有吗
Like, not high at all?
没有 我不想搞砸今天
No. I didn't want to screw today up.
你是不是脑子进水啦
What the hell is wrong with you?
你今天一定要做自己啊
You can't change who you are today.
来的可是《纽约时报》啊
The New York Times is coming.
你要怎么应对啊
How will you cope?
我是说 你哪天是没有抽大麻的
I mean, when's the last time you weren't high?
我出生那天
My birth.
不过我当时很醉
But I was really drunk.
我喝了一瓶红酒呢
I had just had a bottle of wine.
是我妈喝的
Well, my mother had.
我得招待顾客去了
I have to go wait on those customers.
竭尽所能 做你该做的事
Do what you can to get with the program.
我是说 抽你该抽的大麻
I mean, get off the program.
不烘大麻 怎么烘焙
You can't bake not baked.
大玛丽
Big Mary?
约翰
John?
干嘛不叫我的新名字
Why not try my new name?
弃婴加西莫多
Quasimodo.
你这有大麻吗
Do you have any weed?
我有没有大麻
Do I have any weed?
我看看我的驼峰里有没有
Let me check my hump.
没 没有大麻
Nope. No weed.
谢谢 里克 我不问你
Thanks, Rico. I didn't want to ask
是因为全市禁止种族偏见
due to the city-wide ban on racial profiling.
哇 这个洗碗间比
Wow. This dish room is cleaner
克里斯·克里斯蒂吃完午餐后的盘子还干净
than Chris Christie's plate after lunch.
麦克斯 我要两个薰衣草马卡龙
Max, I need two lavender macaroons.
-做好了吗 -正在做
- Where are they? - I'm working on them.
太好了 我为你感到骄傲
Well, good. I'm so proud of you.
这感觉就像电影《怪诞星期五》
This is so Freaky Friday.
薰衣草马卡龙在这里
Here are the lavender macaroons.
瞧 手里握着大麻烟 心里就已乐无边
See? Even just holding this, I'm better.
现在我们只希望不会出什么差错
Now we just have to hope nothing goes wrong.
惊喜吧
Surprise!
我们大家来支持你们了
We all came to support you.
差错送上门了
Well, that's it.
《纽约时报》的美食评论家可能会和
The New York Times food critic may be in the same room
阿憨 厄尔 奥列格 苏菲在同一个餐厅
as Han, Earl, Oleg, and Sophie.
我们死翘翘了 死亡时间11点30分
We're dead. Time of death, 11:30.
我相信应该是4点20分
I believe it's more like 4:20.
卡洛琳 我喜欢你新打工的地方
Oh, Caroline, I love your new place.
环境清新又漂亮
It's so fresh and pretty.
看起来有点像阴道冲洗器的广告
It kind of looks like a douche commercial.
你说得没错 宝贝
You're right, baby.
跟阴道冲洗器的广告一模一样
It looks exactly like a douche commercial.
好吧 咱们能不在高级甜点店
Okay. Can we stop saying "Douche"
说"阴道冲洗器"这个词吗
in the fancy pastry shop?
我同意 太不合适了
I agree. Not appropriate.
卡洛琳 亲爱的 麻烦把我的手机号
Caroline, darling, slip my phone number
偷塞给那位努比亚美女
to that fine Nubian princess.
告诉她不要被我坏了的屁股欺骗
And tell her not to be fooled by my bad hip.
我仍可以温柔地让她升天
I can still gently rock her world.
好啦 伙计们 你们来这干嘛
Okay, guys, what are you doing here
你们能多快离开
and how quickly can you leave?
真"友好"
Real nice.
我们大老远跑来这里只为了
After we came all this way to just order only desserts
点麦克斯会做的甜点
that Max knows how to make
以及夸你是一位好服务员
and to say nice things about you as a waitress.
你会为我这么做吗
Oh, you'd do that for me?
当然不会 我哪演得出来
Hell no, I can't pull that off.
如果我会演戏 我就卖了餐厅
If I could act, I'd sell the restaurant
去任何一家电视台
and get cast in two-line roles as the doctor
演一位只有两句台词的医生
on any network television show.
苏菲是女演员
Sophie's the actress.
相信我 她的演技一级棒
And trust me, she's got quite a repertoire.
在床上 我称她为"梅力了·湿特离谱"
In bed, I call her Meryl Sheets.
露一手 宝贝
Do it, baby.
真是个好地方
Oh, what a lovely place.
模仿了她的口音演我们的电影
That's the accent she uses when we play
《性奴12年》
"12 Years A Sex Slave."
好的 立刻上
Lovely, be right back.
对了 欢迎来到嗨翻天
Oh, and, welcome to The High.
那桌人是怎么回事
What's going on with that table?
最近市里来了欧洲马戏团吗
Is there a European circus in town?
马戏团 我可不知道
A circus? Well, I wouldn't know.
我完全不知道他们是谁
I really have no idea who they are.
我没有要你回答
That didn't require an answer.
我只是让你听听我一语中的的观察结果
It was just one of my dead-on observations.
快把他们赶走
Just get rid of them.
告诉他们我们这里没有漏斗蛋糕了
Tell them we've run out of funnel cakes.
感觉我变回原来的自己了
Well, I'm feeling like my old self.
乔啊让我把阿憨 厄尔 奥列格和苏菲弄走
Joe just told me to lose Han, Earl, Oleg, and Sophie.
我怎么才能把这么多人弄不见啊
How am I supposed to lose that many people?
我又不是空中交通管制人员
I'm not air traffic control.
你说得好像他们不懂在高级地方管好自己
You are acting like they don't know how to act in a fancy place.
姑娘们 快看
Girls, look!
奥列格把餐巾当成派对帽戴
Oleg's wearing his napkin as a party hat.
这是你们的甜点 祝你们好胃口
Here's your dessert. Bon appetite.
麦克斯 真不敢相信那是你做的
Max, I can't believe you just made that.
我也不信
Neither can I.
你对奥列格和苏菲说了什么
And what did you say to Oleg and Sophie?
都过了一个小时了 我还没看见
It's been an hour, and I haven't seen
有任何扫桌上去狂搞的行为
any over-the-table penetration.
我就告诉他们拿出最好的一面
I just told them to be on their best behavior,
他们对此没意见
and they're fine with it.
不好意思 麦克斯
Excuse me, Max.
这里这里
Yes, hi.
我能去尿尿吗
May I go tinkle?
或者这违反了军事监狱甜点店的法律
Or is that against the law here at Guantanamo Dessert Bay?
我要去女厕所做爱
I'm gonna go have sex in the ladies room.
除非假正经的你俩对此也有意见
Unless you two prudes have a problem with that, too.
打扰了
Excuse me.
我能来杯拿铁和红酒吗
Can I get a latte and a red wine?
因为有一颗止痛药卡在我喉咙了
'Cause I got a Vicodin stuck in my throat.
天啊
Oh, my God.
谁会大中午的
Who could be that messed up
就把自己搞成这样啊
in the middle of the afternoon?
我的新闺蜜吗
Uh, my new best friend.
我得在乔啊和时报评论家
I better get rid of her before Joe
进来之间把她弄走
or that Times critic walks in.
你继续无心插柳柳成荫吧
You keep doing good things by accident.
你好 我可以来杯...
Hi, can I get a--
当然可以 不过不是在这里
You sure can. Anywhere but here.
不 我现在不适合转圈
Oh, no. Spinning's not good for me right now.
她在这里干嘛
What is she doing here?
她正要离开 你从未见过她
Leaving. You never saw her.
-等到 -乔啊 我能搞定
- Wait-- - Joe, I got this.
我念书时的闺蜜大约有一周
My bestie at school was totally hooked
沉溺于吃各种处方药
on prescription pills for, like, a week.
你好呀
Hey, hi, you.
打扰了 麦克斯在哪儿
Excuse me. Where is Max?
她去后厨一下
She's in the back for a sec.
所以
So...
我们有缘千里又相会了吗
We meet again.
先生 你有需要什么吗
Sir, do you need something in the back?
是的 卡洛琳说她去给我拿餐巾了
Yes, Caroline said she'd bring me a napkin,
但我接通华纳公司的电话比她办事速度快
but I could get Time Warner on the phone faster than that.
不信问问麦克斯
Just ask Max.
她在餐厅经常帮卡洛琳打掩护
She covers for Caroline all the time at the diner.
麦克斯
Max?
噢 嗨翻天的好戏
Ooh. Drama at The High.
阿憨 这位是我的新老板
Han, that's my new boss.
别说了
Stop talking.
还有别再搜集贴纸了 你都是大人了
Also, stop collecting stickers. You're a grown-up.
好了 我把那位瘾君子扔出去了
Okay, I threw that drug addict out.
那位瘾君子是我的女朋友
That drug addict is my girlfriend.
又一嗨翻天的好戏
More drama at The High.
卡洛琳 我们有个问题
And Caroline, we have a problem.
你居然称艾莉为瘾君子
You called Allie a drug addict.
那是她的名字吗
Oh, is that her name?
艾莉 真可爱
Allie? So cute.
爱到不能行
Even lovelier.
根据那位小小人的话
And according to that very small man,
你还是一名糟糕的服务员
you're also a terrible waitress.
可我当时不知道你们俩是一对啊
But I had no idea you two were together.
我本来以为你的伴侣会是一名很强大...
I would have thought a powerful...
住手
Stop. Now.
乔啊 听着 我们很需要这份工作
Joe, look, we really need these jobs.
我们的烘焙生意决策失误
We made a bad decision with our bakery business,
导致要还一大笔我们还不起的银行贷款
and we have a big bank loan that we can't pay.
诚实 很好
Honesty. Good.
客人们会对诚实有好感
People respond to honesty.
我不喜欢 但他们喜欢
I don't, but they do.
麦克斯 你在这里很有潜力
Max, you have potential here.
卡洛琳 作为一名女服务员你被解雇了
Caroline, you're fired as a waitress.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
住手
Stop!
里面没料可以救你
There's nothing in there to save you.
好吧 如果要炒她 那连我也炒了吧
Well, if she's fired, I'm fired, too.
别紧张 诺玛蕾
Oh, relax, Norma Rae.
她作为一名女服务员被解雇了
She's fired as a waitress,
但她被聘请为一名领座员
but she's hired as a hostess.
是吗 为什么
I am? Why?
因为你长得漂亮 秒露了一个咪咪
Because you're pretty, you flashed a boob,
而且你五分钟内就能控制住艾莉
and you took more control of Allie in five minutes
比过去她去的三个勒戒所里的任何人都厉害
than anybody's been able to do in her three rehab stints.
而这 姑娘 就是纽约需要的领座员
And that, lady, is a New York City hostess.
姑娘们 我被三振出局了
Well, girls, I struck out.
比尔·科斯比毁掉了所有70岁以上的黑人
Bill Cosby has ruined it for all black men over 70
请年轻姑娘喝一杯的机会
who are just trying to buy a gal a drink.
麦克斯 你觉得怎么样
Max, how do you like that?
我是领座员 我升职啦
I'm the hostess. I got a promotion!
我不认为领座员是升职
I don't think a hostess is a promo--
就是 麦克斯 因为银行余额是负数
It is, Max, 'cause with a less-than-zero bank balance,
这必须是 这是我仅存的乐事了
it has to be. It's all I have left.